Guide to the Bruce J. Zobel Papers, 1937-2008 MC 00259
Special Collections Research Center
- Symposia and Conferences, 1937-1993; MC 00259 Series 11
  - Genetics
    - Statistical Considerations in Genetic Testing of Forest Trees. Southern Regional information Exchange Group 40. Southern Cooperative Series Bulletin No. 324. Gainesville, Florida: Institute of Food and Agricultural Sciences, University of Florida, 1986; Formerly Box 64b (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - XIV Reunion del Grupo de Mejoramiento Genetico Forestal. Comision Forestal de America del Norte. Durango, 1984; Formerly Box 64b (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Progeny Testing: Proceedings of Servicewide Genetics Workshop, Charleston, South Carolina, December 5-9, 1983. Washington, D.C.: USDA Forest Service, Timber Management, 1984; Formerly Box 64b (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - "Proceedings from the Nordic Tree Breeders Meeting, September 1990, Horsholm, Denmark: Consequences of Modern Techniques in Tree Breeding for Breeding Strategies." Forest Tree Improvement, No. 23. Copenhagen, Denmark: Akademisk Forlag, 1987; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Working Group on Quantitative Genetics. New Orleans: Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, and US Department of Agriculture, 1970; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Association Canadienne pour l'Amelioration de Arbres / Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Programme. Sainte-Foy, Quebec, Canada, 1997; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Pulkkinen, Pertti. Reports from the Foundation for Forest Tree Breeding 5. Biological Systems in Breeding. Helsinki, 1992; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Kozubov, G.M., E.M. Marlin, Yu E. Novitskaya, and R.M. Sboeva. Conference on Forest-Tree Genetics, Selection, and Seed Production. Translated from Russian. Jerusalem: Israel Program for Scientific Translations, 1967; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Salazar, Rodolfo. Manejo y Aprovechamiento de Plantaciones Forestales con Especies de Uso Multiple. Guatemala: Centro Agronomico Tropical de Investigacion y Ensenanza, Catie, 1989; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Mass Production Technology for Genetically Improved Fast Growing Forest Tree Species. Resumes - Summaries. Symposium Bordeaux France, 1992; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Lambeth, Clements and William Dvorak. "Resolving Tropical Forest Resource Concerns Through Tree Improvement, Gene Conservation and Domestication of New Species." Breeding Tropical Trees. Colombia: IUFRO, 1992; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Nordic Group of Forest Tree Breeders. Tudia Forestalia Suecica. No. 166. Uppsala, Sweden: Swedish University of Agriculture Sciences, 1984; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Thirty Eight Annual National Poultry Breeders Roundtable. St. Louis, Missouri: Poultry Breeders of America and Southeastern Poultry and Egg Association, 1989; Formerly Box 64C (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Experimentell Genekologi/Experimental Genecology. Lectures from a conference in Stockholm, November 15-16, 1977. Department of Forest Genetics Research Notes No. 27. Garpenberg, Sweden: Royal College of Forestry, Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 1)
      [Swedish]
    - Proceedings of the Symposium on Variation and Breeding Systems of Triplochiton scleroxylon (K. Schum.). Held at the Federal Dept. of Forest Research, Ibadan, Nigeria, April 21-28, 1975, Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of a Forest Genetics Workshop. Held in Macon, Georgia, October 25-27, 1962. Southern Forest Tree Improvement Committee, 1963; Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Seventh North American Forest Biology Workshop Program and Abstracts. Held at the University of Kentucky, Lexington, Kentucky, July 26-28, 1982, Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the Working Group on Quantitative Genetics of Section 22, IUFRO, Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - IUFRO Conference-A Joint Meeting of Working Parties on Breeding Theory, Progeny Testing, and Seed Orchards: Conference Proceedings. Held in Williamsburg, Virginia, October 12-18, 1986. Hosted by the North Carolina State University-Industry Cooperative Tree Improvement Program, [no date], Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Program Agenda and Abstracts of Invited and Volunteer Papers of the IUFRO Conference. Hosted by the North Carolina State University-Industry Cooperative Tree Improvement Program. Williamsburg, Virginia, 1986; Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Research Needs in Tree Breeding: Proceedings of the 15th North American Quantitative Forest Genetics Group Workshop. Held in Coeur d'Alene, Idaho, August 6-8, 1981. Raleigh, North Carolina: School of Forest Resources, NCSU, Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings of a Meeting of the Working Party on Progeny Testing. Held at the Georgia Forestry Center, Macon, Georgia, October 25-27, 1972. Georgia Forest Research Council, Formerly Box 64D (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings of the World Consultation on Forest Genetics and Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Stockholm, August 23-30, 1963. Volume 1., Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts of the U.S.-China Cooperative Science Program Seminar on Forest Ecology and Genetics. Held in Taipei, Republic of China, March 31-April 8, 1972., Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - "Symposium on Nordic Co-operation in the Field of Plant Breeding," held in Helsinki, Finland, November 30-December 4, 1981. Edited by Rolf Manner and Bjorn Sigurbjornsson. Acta Agriculturae Scandinavica, Supplement 23. Stockholm, Sweden, 1983; Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Skogliga Genresurser/Forest Genetic Resources. Symposium held in Ultuna, Sweden, 1976. Stockholm: Department of Forest Genetics, Royal College of Forestry, 1977; Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Progeny Testing of Forest Trees. Proceedings of Workshop on Progeny Testing, held in Auburn, Alabama, June 15-16, 1982. Southern Cooperative Series Bulletin No. 275, February 1983; Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Granforadling (Breeding Norway Spruce): Bogesund 1976. Conference held at Roskar, Bogesund, January 20-21, 1976. Stockholm, Sweden: The Department of Forest Genetics, The Swedish College of Forestry, Stockholm, Sweden [in Swedish], Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the Ninth Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada, Part II: Reports and Papers. Held at Petawawa Forest Experiment Station, September 16-18, 1964. Ottawa: Department of Forestry of Canada, Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Advanced Generation Breeding of Forest Trees. Proceedings of a Workshop on Advanced Generation Breeding: Current Status and Research Needs. Held in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, June 6-7, 1984. Southern Cooperative Series Bulletin No. 309. Louisiana Agricultural Experiment Station, June 1986; Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Moglichkeiten der Beurteilung von Auslesebaumen der Forstpflanzenzuchtungz. Tagungsberichte, Number 69. 1965. [in German], Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - "Hybrids of the Slash-Caribbean-Central American Pines Complex: Characteristics, Bases of Superiority and Potential Utility in South China and Elsewhere," by D.G. Nikles. Asia-Pacific Symposium on Forest Genetic Improvement, held in Beijing, October 19-22, 1994 (Box 382, Folder 15)
    - IUFRO Joint Conference of Division 2: "Forest Genetics and Tree Breeding in the Age of Genomics: Progress and Future," Charleston, South Carolina, November 1-5, 2004 (Box 382, Folder 16)
  - Pulp and Paper
    - Abstracts of Sixth TAPPI Forest Biology Conference. Held at the Institute of Paper Chemistry, Appleton Wisconsin, May 1-3, 1972., Formerly Box 64E (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - 1975 TAPPI Annual Meeting Preprint. Held in New York, New York, February 24-26, 1975. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, 1974; Formerly Box 64F (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - 1974 TAPPI Forest Biology Conference. Held in Seattle, Washington, September 18-20, 1974. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64F (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - TAPPI 1974 Annual Meeting. Held January 14-16, 1974. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64F (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - 1977 TAPPI Annual Meeting. Held in Atlanta, Georgia, February 14-16, 1977. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64F (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Forest Biology Wood Chemistry Conference 1977. Held in Madison, Wisconsin, June 20-22, 1977. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64F (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - 1978 TAPPI Annual Meeting. Held in Chicago, Illinois, March 6-8, 1978. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64F (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - 1982 Research and Development Division Conference. Held in Asheville, North Carolina, August 29-September 1, 1982. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64G (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - 1981 TAPPI Annual Meeting Proceedings. Held in Chicago, Illinois, March 2-5, 1981. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64G (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - 1980 TAPPI Annual Meeting Proceedings. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64G (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - 1979 TAPPI Annual Meeting Proceedings. Held in New York, New York, March 12-14, 1979. Atlanta, Georgia: Technical Association of the Pulp and Paper Industry, Formerly Box 64G (Box 133, Folder 4)
    - 70th Annual Meeting, Technical Section, Canadian Pulp & Paper Association. Held in Montreal, Quebec, February 2-3, 1984. Montreal, Quebec: Canadian Pulp & Paper Association, Formerly Box 64H (Box 64.08, Folder 1)
    - "The Amazon Forest and the Pulp Industry: What Are the Facts?" by Leopoldo Garcia Brandao, Marlet Pulp 7 Conference, May 21-22, 1990 (Box 382, Folder 17)
  - Society of American Foresters
    - Proceedings of the 57th Annual Meeting of the Appalachian Section, Society of American Foresters. Held in Raleigh, NC, February 1-3, 1978. Richmond, VA: Appalachian Section, Society of American Foresters, Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 47th Annual Meeting of the Appalachian Section, Society of American Foresters. Held in Raleigh, NC, February 8-9, 1968. Charlottesville, VA: Appalachian Section, Society of American Foresters, Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the Society of American Foresters Meeting. Held in Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1947. Washington, DC: Society of American Foresters, Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the Society of American Foresters Meeting: "Our Changing Forests." Held in Milwaukee, 1954. Washington, DC: Society of American Foresters, 1955; Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the Society of American Foresters Meeting: "Converting the Old-Growth Forest." Held in Portland, Oregon, 1955. Washington, DC: Society of American Foresters, 1956; Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the Society of American Foresters Meeting: "Forest Land Use in Transition." Held in Syracuse, New York, 1957. Washington, DC: Society of American Foresters, 1958; Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 7)
    - Proceedings of the Society of American Foresters Meeting: "Forestry and People." Held in San Francisco, California, 1959. Washington, DC: Society of American Foresters, 1960; Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings of the Society of American Foresters Meeting: "Southern Forestry on the March." Held in Atlanta, Georgia, 1962. Washington, DC: Society of American Foresters, 1963; Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings of 39th Annual Meeting Appalachian Section Society of American Foresters, 1960; Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 10)
    - Appalachian Section: 42nd Annual Meeting Proceedings. Held in Greenville, South Carolina, February 8-9, 1963, Formerly Box 64H (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - S.J. Hall Lectureship in Industrial Forestry, University of California-Berkeley
    - "The Small Timber Company - An Endangered Species," by William Holmes, May 26, 1970 (Box 382, Folder 18)
    - "The Consultant - Everyman's Forester," by John G. Miles, May 13, 1971 (Box 382, Folder 19)
    - "Growing 40,000 Homes a Year," by W.D. Hagenstein, April 26, 1973 (Box 382, Folder 20)
    - "Increasing Productivity of Forest Lands Through Better Trees," by Bruce Zobel, April 18, 1974 (Box 382, Folder 21)
    - "The South's Third Forest: Implications for the Future," by Arthur W. Nelson, Jr., April 13, 1976 (Box 383, Folder 1)
    - "You, Gifford Pinchot and the Ladies of the Massachusetts Bay Colony," by Leonard B. Netzorg, April 21, 1977 (Box 383, Folder 2)
    - "Federal Timber Policy and Private Timber Prospects," by George A. Craig, 1980 (Box 383, Folder 3)
    - "Is The Family Forest Feasible?" by Hardin R. Glascock, Jr., April 16, 1981 (Box 383, Folder 4)
    - "Politics, Policies, Regulation and Forestry in the Redwoods: Three Decades of Recollection," by Henry K. Trobitz, April 1982 (Box 383, Folder 5)
    - "The Legislative and Regulatory Environment for Forestry Enterprises in California," by Stephen L. DeMaria, May 13, 1983 (Box 383, Folder 6)
    - "Of Forestry, Tree Spikers, and the Dinosaur," by Harold R. Walt, November 18, 1986 (Box 383, Folder 7)
    - "Power Brokers: Is the Network Closed?" by William N. Dennison, November 19, 1987 (Box 383, Folder 8)
    - "European Forestry: A Global Perspective," by John Campbell, February 23, 1989 (Box 383, Folder 9)
    - "A 75-Year Perspective on Investments in Forestry," by John A. Zivnuska, October 12, 1989 (Box 383, Folder 10)
    - "Simpson: A Century of Growth and Future Prospects," by John L. Walker, October 18, 1990 (Box 383, Folder 11)
    - "Striking a Balance: A Perspective on Managing Our Forest Resource," by Dan Tomascheski, November 21, 1991 (Box 383, Folder 12)
    - "Watersheds, Landscapes, Biodiversity, Fire & Forest Management," by Henry Alden, December 1, 1992 (Box 383, Folder 13)
  - Tree Improvement Conferences
    - Canadian
      - Proceedings of the Seventeenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Part 2. Held in Gander, Newfoundland, August 27-30, 1979. Edited by M.A.K. Khalil. Ottawa, Canada: Canadian Forestry Service, Environment Canada, for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1980; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of the Fifteenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association: Part 2. Held in Petawawa Forest Experiment Station, Chalk River, Canada, August 18-22, 1975. Edited by E.K. Morgenstern. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service, Department of the Environment for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1976; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 2)
        [in English and French]
      - Proceedings of the Eighth Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada. Part 2: Progress Reports. Held in Fredericton, New Brunswick, Canada, August 16-18, 1962. Ottawa, Forest Research Branch, Department of Forestry, [no date, in English and French], Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Seventeenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Part 1: Minutes and Members' reports. Held in Gander, Newfoundland, August 27-30, 1979. Edited by C.W. Yeatman. Ottawa, Canada: Canadian Forestry Service, Environment Canada, for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1980; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 4)
      - Proceedings of the Eleventh Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada. Part 2: Reports, Papers, and Abstracts. Edited by C.W. Yeatman. Ottawa: Forestry Branch, Department of Fisheries and Forestry of Canada, 1969; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the Sixteenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association: Part 2. Held at the University of Manitoba, Winnipeg, Canada, June 27-30, 1977. Edited by A.G. Corriveau and C.W. Yeatman. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service, Department of Fisheries and the Environment for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1978; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 6)
      - Proceedings of the Seventh Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada. Part 2: Reports and Reviews. Held at Cowichan Lake, Canada, August 21-23, 1960. Ottawa, Forest Research Branch, Canada Department of Forestry, [no date], Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 7)
      - Tree Improvement-Progressing Together: Proceedings of the Twenty-first Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Part 2. Held in Truro, Nova Scotia, Canada, August 17-21, 1987. Edited by E.K. Morgenstern and T.J.B. Boyle. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1988; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 8)
      - Proceedings of the Sixth Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada. Held in Montreal, Canada, August 17-19, 1958. Part 2: Reports and Papers. Ottawa: Forest Research Division, Forestry Branch Canada, Department of Northern Affairs and National Resources, [no date], Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 9)
      - Proceedings of the Fourteenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association: Part 2. Held in Fredericton, New Brunswick, Canada, August 28-30, 1973. Edited by D.P. Fowler and C.W. Yeatman. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service, Department of the Environment for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1975; Formerly Box 64J (Box 135, Folder 10)
      - Tree Improvement Symposium. Conference Proceedings. Toronto, Ontario: Canada-Ontario Joint Forestry Research Committee, 1979; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of the Fifth Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada. Held in Petawawa, Canada, September 19-20, 1957. Part 2: Reports and Papers. Ottawa: Forest Research Division, Forestry Branch Canada, Department of Northern Affairs and National Resources, [no date], Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - Proceedings of the Eighteenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. [front cover missing, binding deteriorating], Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Nineteenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Part 1: Minutes and Members' Reports. Held in Toronto, Ontario, August 22-26, 1983. Edited by C.W. Yeatman. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service, Environment Canada, for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1984; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - Clonal Forestry: Its Impact on Tree Improvement and our Future Forests: Proceedings of the Nineteenth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Part 2. Held in Toronto, Ontario, August 22-26, 1983. Edited by L. Zsuffa, R.M. Rauter, and C.W. Yeatman. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1985; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - New Ways in Forest Genetics: Proceedings of the Twentieth Meeting of the Canadian Tree Improvement Association. Part 2. Held in Quebec City, Quebec, August 19-22, 1985. Edited by F. Caron, A.G. Corriveau, and T.J.B. Boyle. Ottawa: Canadian Forestry Service for the Canadian Tree Improvement Association, 1986; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - Proceedings of the Tenth Meeting of the Committee on Forest Tree Breeding in Canada. Part 2: Reports and Papers. Held jointly with the Western Forest Genetics Association at the University of British Columbia, Vancouver, B.C., September 7-10, 1966. Ottawa: Forestry Branch, Department of Forestry and Rural Development of Canada, 1967; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Central States
      - Proceedings of the First Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Wooster, October 8-9, 1959. Ohio Agricultural Experiment Station and the Central States Forest Experiment Station Forest Service, USDA, August, 1960; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 8)
      - Proceedings of the Third Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Lafayette, Indiana, October 1962. Edited by Arthur H. Westing. Lafayette, Indiana: Department of Forestry and Conservation, Purdue University, June, 1963; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 9)
      - Proceedings of the Fourth Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Lincoln, Nebraska, October 1-3, 1964. Edited by Ralph A. Read. Lincoln, Nebraska: Nebraska Agricultural Experiment Station, June, 1965; Formerly Box 64K (Box 136, Folder 10)
      - Proceedings of the Fifth Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the Ohio Agricultural Research and Development Center, Wooster, Ohio, October 6-7, 1966. Edited by H.B. Kriebel. Wooster, Ohio: Ohio Agricultural Research and Development Center, June, 1967; Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of the Sixth Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Carbondale, Illinois and St. Louis, Missouri, October 16-18, 1968. Edited by David T. Funk. St. Paul, Minnesota and Carbondale, Illinois: North Central Forest Experiment Station, USDA Forest Service and Department of Forestry, School of Agriculture, Southern Illinois University, [no date], Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - Proceedings of the Eighth Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Columbia, Missouri, October 11-13, 1972. Edited by R. Brooks Polk. Columbia, Missouri: School of Forestry, Fisheries and Wildlife, University of Missouri-Columbia, August, 1974; Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Ninth Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Ames, Iowa, October 10-11, 1974. Edited by Calvin F Bey. Upper Darby, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Area, State and Private Forestry, [no date], Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - Proceedings of the Tenth Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at Purdue University, West Lafayette, Indiana, September 22-23, 1976. Edited by Walter F. Beineke. West Lafayette, Indiana: Department of Forestry and Natural Resources, Purdue University, [no date], Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the First North Central Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Madison, Wisconsin, August 21-23, 1979. Edited by R.P. Guries. Madison, Wisconsin: North Central Tree Improvement Association, [no date], Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 6)
      - Proceedings of the Second North Central Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Lincoln, Nebraska, August 5-7, 1981. Edited by R.P. Guries. Madison, Wisconsin: North Central Tree Improvement Association, [no date], Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 7)
      - Proceedings of the Third North Central Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Wooster, Ohio, August 17-19, 1983. Edited by R.P. Guries. Madison, Wisconsin: North Central Tree Improvement Association, [no date], Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 8)
      - Proceedings of the Second Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held in Franklin Park, Illinois, October 12-13, 1960. Illinois Agricultural Experiment Station, Urbana, Illinois, July, 1962; Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Southern
      - Report of the First Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Held in Atlanta, Georgia, January 9-10, 1951. Atlanta, Georgia: U.S. Forest Service, Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 10)
      - Report of the Second Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Held in Atlanta, Georgia, January 6-7, 1953. Atlanta, Georgia: U.S. Forest Service, Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 11)